I love the day of Brahma, a football fan,
люблю день брахмы болельщик футбольный
this is the ultimate, far from football,
на это конечная далекие от футбола
I’m from Ukraine, the city of Khmelnitsky,
вблизи я из украины города хмельницкий
which city of
вы из какого города
Saratov are you from
саратов родовая у людей из россии
?  war in order to
что надо было объявлять войну чтобы
talk about war to declare war on the basis of
говорить о войне объявить на основании
which you made such a conclusion what place
чего вы сделали такой вывод какого места
is
на
super super
супер супер
good as a lawyer lawyer and I ask you if
хорошо как юрист юрист а вас прошу если
you just found about the war on
вы только что про войну отыскали на
which document camera the motive on the right
какой документной камер мотив на правой
obt you rely on tell me in which
обт вы опираетесь скажите мне в каком
document what norm is written  that war
документе какой норме написано что война
is the one when it was officially declared
это та когда ее объявили официально
some kind of document tell me here I am on
какой-никакой документ скажите вот я на
google and now
google и сейчас
several kaido losses lawyer coming out of the
несколько кайдо убытках юрист выходе из
sky yenisei then as a lawyer lawyer
неба енисей затем как юристу юрист у
tell me which document says that
скажите в каком документе сказано что
war should be declared
войну надо объявлять
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
well tell me when in what  in which
хорошо скажите мне когда в каком в каком
document to
документе
read about the procedure for declaring
почитать про то про порядок объявления
war, well,
войны
just what is the decision  I’m
чтож только что такое решение ген
leaving the gene as it’s specifically called,
оставляю как конкретно называется
for example,
например
I just finally found a lawyer, as a
я просто наконец-то юриста нашел я как
lawyer I found a lawyer who the
юрист нашел юриста который мне сейчас
document will tell me now, let’s
документ скажет давайте
book my face specifically into the norm in
книги меня мордой конкретно в норму в
which the scan, here’s the war you need to declare
которой скана вот войну нужно объявлять
that I usually communicated with people as ordinary
что я обычно с людьми общался обычными
hard workers, you are a lawyer, this is very  cool with a
работягами вы юрист это очень круто с
lawyer we can talk about specific norms
юристом можем говорить о конкретных норм
specifically open to your wife tell me which
конкретно откройте жене скажите какой
point I’ll tell you that we need to declare war,
пункт раскажу что надо объявить войну
look here I opened the Geneva
смотрите вот я открыл женевскую
Convention so
конвенцию так
there’s nothing there about declaring war
там ничего нету про объявления войны
tell me what your Geneva Convention is called
скажите как называется ваша женевской
that we understood whether we
конвенции что мы поняли ли мы по
have already
одинаковой уже несколько
been called civil by the same name
ого называется
we opened this very document where
мы открыли один этот самый документ где
it says that you need to declare it
там сказано что вы ему надо объявлять
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
you watched the bagels of the wildebeest, it’s you the
вы смотрели баранки гну это вы ответ
lawyer
юриста
’s answer about everything the lawyer disappeared if only they were all
о все юрист пропал вот бы их всех
trying to jump up a specific norm so
пытаясь вскочить конкретную норму так
that says that war is the one when
которая говорит что война это та когда
war was declared and
войну объявили и
you write  essay there international law
вы написать эссе там международном праве
so because there is no such sweat  mu what
так потому что нету такого потому что
when this I am in the south with 20 years of experience ok
когда этот я юге с 20-летним стажем ok
lawyer 20 years of staff and my face mimay
юрист 20-летний штат и меня морду мимэй
face into a specific document tell
мордой в конкретный документ скажи вот
you where it says that war must be
тебе где написано что война должна быть
declared otherwise this is not war some
объявлена иначе это не война какая-то
[ __ ] like a special operation so
фигня типа спецоперации так
funny from these towers  moments sophia will
смешные от башни эти моменты софия тебя
bend you down the puppy
нагну щенок
Ukrainians put me in the place of each
украинцы моим ставите на месте каждого
such piglet to the life-
такого поросят к
giving their places in the barn and you
живоносного свои места в хлеву и по вы
don’t
не
you to you with their nose specifically in their
ты к ты их носом конкретно в ихнем
nonsense as the street is called a special
брехню как улица называется специальной
military operation so that you have the
военной операции для то чтобы у ника ты
words of wine for your nose and  get out and fight
для своего носа слова вина а вон и воюют
so the tour is additionally full-scale
так туре дополнительно полномасштабно
fault so for rocket attacks from
вина так за ракетным обстрелам из
aviation
авиацию
software you will
software you
hit the fleet so it’s not fault about their
заденем флоту так это не вина об их
mission kum some people their engineering end
мишне кум одни люди их инженерская конец
opens the view of the curves of the Geneva
открывается вид кривов женевскую
convention on purpose so you
конвенцию специально так вы
absolutely can’t process not a
абсолютно не мая процес не
word I’m at the tower of these yet  an excerpt on him is
слову я у башни этих еще отрывок на ему
true to us water view blasting the church
верна нас воды вид взрывание костел
fart from him so I bachu bachu whom
пукана у него так вот я бачу бачу кого
you start others by
ты начинай иных мимо
a romantic and a view of 20 for your husband and you
а романтик и вид 20 за твой муж и ты
t  like
таки
three muscles position spa device floor
три мышцы позиция спа девайс этаж
charged with positive
зарядилась позитивом
direct ability subscribe to the channel
прямо имость подписывайтесь на канал
dismissed jade and our mind peter
распустил джейд и наши виду петр
imitation channel subscribe to the
имитацией канал подписывайтесь на
kilogram and we will fry and gave glory to
килограммчик и будем жарить и дали слава
ukraine
украине